<Questionare>
    <Item>
        <Title>YODA-THE CAT WITH FOUR EARS</Title>
        <Text>
            In Chicago, Illinois, couple Valerie and Ted Rock took the cat in two years ago after they visited a local bar, where a group of drinkers were handing the animal around and making fun of him.
            Since being adopted by the Rocks and after getting his picture posted on the Internet, the two-year-old cat immediately became famous.
            The Rocks have received calls from Good Morning America, Fox News and The Tyra Banks Show.
            His pictures are shown in many magazines.
            People are surprised at his extra pair of ears.
            Despite his strange appearance, Yoda - named after the pointy-eared Star Wars character - is a perfectly normal and attractive cat.
            His extra ears are thought to be the result of a genetic mutation.
            He likes being taken for a walk with his owners.
            But Yoda's owners are keeping a close watch on their much-loved pet.
            They are concerned he could be catnapped because he is so different.
        </Text>
    </Item>

    <Item>
        <Title>Salt coffee – Last Part</Title>
        <Text>
            After 40 years, he passed away, and left her a letter which said:
            “My dearest, please forgive me, forgive my life's lie.
            This was the only lie I said to you - the salty coffee.
            Remember the first time we dated?
            I was so nervous at that time, actually I wanted some sugar, but I said salt, it was hard for me to change so I just went ahead.
            I never thought that would be the start of my biggest lie.
            I tried to tell you the truth many times in my life, but I was too afraid to, as I had promised never to lie to you.
            Now I’m dying, and afraid of nothing so I will tell you the truth: I don’t like salty coffee, what a strange bad taste!
            But I have had salty coffee for my whole life.
            Since I have known you, I have never felt sorry for anything I have done for you.
            Having you with me is the biggest happiness of my life.
            If I could live again, I would want to know you and have you for my whole life, even if I had to drink the salty coffee again.”
            Her tears made the letter totally wet.
            Some day, someone asked her: "How does salty coffee taste?" "It’s sweet," she replied.
        </Text>
    </Item>

    <Item>

        <Title>Dating</Title>
        <Text>
            One day in the 1920’s, a young man asked if he could visit a woman at her home. When he arrived at her home, she was wearing a hat on her head.
            Many people today may not understand what this story means. But any American in the 1920’s would understand. The hat said that the girl would like to go out with him.
            In the past, men liked sitting in the girl’s house to talk, to meet her mother, to have something to eat and to listen to her play the piano. However women would like to go on a date, to go out to somewhere interesting.
            This new style of dating began to take the place of the old system of visiting in society in the early 20th century. Nowadays, it is very popular around the world.
        </Text>
    </Item>

    <Item>

        <Title>Reasons of love</Title>
        <Text>
            When choosing a partner for life what do people usually think of? A recent study has shown that these following factors are the most important things that one takes into consideration when choosing his/her partner. Firstly, beauty is an important factor.
            Although many people say that the partner’s appearance is not important, research has shown that beauty has great effect. Secondly, money is also as important as appearance.
            Rich people are easier to attract the opposite sex than the poor. Both men and women say that they think much on how much money their partners have before they decide to get married.
            In addition, timing is important, if the partner comes in time, marriage is more possible. Do you see? If your partner comes when you are available or eager to love, he will be accepted easily.
        </Text>
    </Item>

    <Item>

        <Title>Attractiveness in American culture</Title>
        <Text>
            In a test done in the 1970s, 1,031 students at the University of Wyoming said what they considered attractive in their partners. Their answers were not new.
            Men tended to prefer blondes, blue eyes and light skin color, while women liked darker men.
            However, there were some surprises. Few men liked very large breasts or boyish women. Almost none of the women liked very muscular men. In fact, both men and women prefer the average.
            Too short, too tall, too pale or too dark were not chosen. Averageness still wins. In a recent study, scientists chose 94 faces of American women and used the computer to make a picture of an average face.
            Then they asked people which face they liked. Of the 94 real faces, only 4 faces were considered to be more attractive than the average face. Most people said that they preferred the average face
        </Text>
    </Item>

    <Item>

        <Title>Young children play sports - Advantages and disadvantages</Title>
        <Text>
            Most kids love to play sports. It’s important to them, but for the majority, it’s just one type of activity out of many that they do.
            For a small number of kids, though, a sport becomes their whole life. They spend almost all their time and energy practicing. This has both advantages and disadvantages.
            Sports are good for young children in many ways. Kids who enjoy sports are likely to have better health. They develop good habits of daily exercise that will keep them healthy as adults, too.
            Today, many children and adults are overweight, but those who love sports stay in shape. Plus, by developing their physical abilities, they will learn how to work hard towards a goal.
            Their achievements in sports will make them feel good about themselves. They’ll also make friends and learn teamwork. Sports, whether a little or a lot, can have positive effects.
            We admire the talent and dedication of young athletes, but we also wonder if they’re losing something. Their focus is very narrow.
            If they devote most of their time to sports, are they neglecting schoolwork? What about other interests? Children should try out many different activities. In addition, many young athletes are pressured by parents or coaches to succeed.
            Kids whose drive comes from inside usually do okay, but others can be unhappy and have health and emotional problems. So sports, like anything else in excess, can have negative effects too.
        </Text>
    </Item>

    <Item>

        <Title>The Panama Canal</Title>
        <Text>
            Most kids love to play sports. It’s important to them, but for the majority, it’s just one type of activity out of many that they do.
            For a small number of kids, though, a sport becomes their whole life. They spend almost all their time and energy practicing. This has both advantages and disadvantages.
            Sports are good for young children in many ways. Kids who enjoy sports are likely to have better health. They develop good habits of daily exercise that will keep them healthy as adults, too.
            Today, many children and adults are overweight, but those who love sports stay in shape. Plus, by developing their physical abilities, they will learn how to work hard towards a goal.
            Their achievements in sports will make them feel good about themselves. They’ll also make friends and learn teamwork. Sports, whether a little or a lot, can have positive effects.
            We admire the talent and dedication of young athletes, but we also wonder if they’re losing something. Their focus is very narrow.
            If they devote most of their time to sports, are they neglecting schoolwork? What about other interests? Children should try out many different activities. In addition, many young athletes are pressured by parents or coaches to succeed.
            Kids whose drive comes from inside usually do okay, but others can be unhappy and have health and emotional problems. So sports, like anything else in excess, can have negative effects too.
        </Text>
    </Item>

    <Item>

        <Title>The Empire State Building</Title>
        <Text>
            The Empire State Building is a 102-story skyscraper in New York City at the intersection of Fifth Avenue and West 34th Street. Its name is derived from the nickname for the state of New York.
            It stood as the world's tallest building for more than forty years, from its completion in 1931 until the construction of the World Trade Center's North Tower was completed in 1972.
            Following the destruction of the World Trade Center in 2001, the Empire State Building once again became the tallest building in New York City and New York State.
            The Empire State Building has been one of the Seven Wonders of the Modern World. The building and its street floor interior are designated landmarks of the New York City Preservation Commission, and confirmed by the New York City Board of Estimate.
            It was designated as a National Historic Landmark in 1986. In 2007, it ranked number one on the List of America's Favorite Architecture sights according to the AIA. The building is owned and managed by W and H Properties.
            The Empire State Building is the second tallest skyscraper in the Americas (surpassed only by Chicago's Willis Tower) and the 11th tallest in the world. The Empire State building is currently undergoing a $120 million renovation in an effort to transform the building into a more energy efficient and eco-friendly structure.
        </Text>
    </Item>

    <Item>

        <Title>The Itaipu Dam</Title>
        <Text>
            The Itaipu Dam is found on the Paean river, close to the Brazil - Paraguay border. The dam is located in the Parana region in Brazil, close to Iguassu Falls. It has one of the world's largest hydro-electric power stations.
            There had been many droughts in Brazil and Paraguay. The governments in both countries wanted to use water from the rivers effectively. They wanted to have enough water for the people in their homes.
            Farmers needed water for crops and for cattle. Factories and industries also needed water. It was necessary that a dam must be built.
            There are many advantages that the Itaipu Dam brings. Firstly, the water from the reservoir is used to supply homes and factories for the south, south-eastern and mid-eastern regions of Brazil. It also supplies water to many homes and factories in Paraguay.
            Secondly, farmers can use the water from the reservoir to irrigate (water) their crops. They can also use the water for their cattle and animals to drink. The farmers can also collect water from the River Parana.
            Some of the gates in the Itaipu Dam are left open so that the water level in the River Parana is the same level throughout the year. Moreover, people can now visit the Iguassu National Park to look at the wildlife there. Before the dam was built, there was no road and it was difficult to travel there.
            In addition, the dam is also a hydroelectric power station. There are 18 turbines or engines in the dam wall. These turbines are turned by the water to make electricity. Cables take the electricity to homes and factories in Brazil and Paraguay. Without electricity people would not be able to watch television, or use fridges and electric appliances. There would also be no lighting.
        </Text>
    </Item>

    <Item>

        <Title>Birthday Traditions</Title>
        <Text>
            The tradition of birthday parties started a long time ago. People thought that there was a special danger from evil spirits on birthdays so friends and family came together to bring good thoughts and wishes and even presents.
            In the past, only kings had a birthday party, but as time went by, the public began to have their own birthday parties. There are some different traditions in different countries around the world.
            In China, everyone celebrates their birthday on New Year’s Day. And on a child’s second birthday, family members put many things on the floor around the child. According to Chinese tradition, the first thing the child picks up will tell us what job the child will choose later in life.
            In some countries, a 21st birthday cake often has a key on top or the cake itself is sometimes in a shape of a key. The key means that the young person is now old enough to leave and enter the family home at any time they want to.
            For Japanese children, the third, fifth and seventh birthdays are particularly important. There’s usually a special party on these birthdays.
        </Text>
    </Item>
</Questionare>
